<?xml version="1.0"?>
<RECORDS>
<TITLE>'Rusters'. The corrosive action of palmar sweat: I. Sodium chloride in sweat.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Inflammatory middle ear diseases in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Precipitating antibodies against Escherichia coli, Bacteroides fragilis ss. thetaiotaomicron and Pseudomonas aeruginosa in serum from normal persons and cystic fibrosis patients, determined by means of crossed immunoelectrophoresis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Exocrine pancreatic insufficiency, small intestinal dysfunction and protein intolerance. A chance occurrence or a connection?.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Increased intracranial pressure in infants with cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Precipitating antibodies against Haemophilus influenzae and Staphylococcus aureus in sputum and serum from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>IgA and IgG antibodies against surface antigens of Pseudomonas aeruginosa in sputum and serum from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Activated complement in the sputum from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Autoantibodies in serum and sputum from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Chronic obstructive lung disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Meconium in health and in disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The effect of oral zinc supplementation on plasma levels of vitamin A and retinol-binding protein in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The fecal microflora and bile acids in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum glycine-conjugated bile acids in pediatric hepatobiliary disorders.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Comparison of the chloride electrode and gravimetric chloride titration sweat tests.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Comparison of the errors due to the use of gauze and the use of filter paper in the gravimetric chloride titration sweat test.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis with acute hypoelectrolytemia and metabolic alkalosis in infancy.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Demineralization in cystic fibrosis detected by direct photon absorptiometry.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Psychosocial support for adults with cystic fibrosis: a group approach.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in adults. 75 cases and a review of 232 cases in the literature.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Genetic counseling and prenatal diagnosis of cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Quantitative evaluation of the development of the exocrine pancreas in cystic fibrosis and control infants.</TITLE>
<TITLE>A comparative study of inhaled atropine sulfate and isoproterenol hydrochloride in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The pulmonary circulation: remodeling in growth and disease. The 1978 J. Burns Amberson lecture.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Aspergillosis and atopy in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Maximal expiratory flows after postural drainage.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Relationship between response to exercise and allergy in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Radioimmunoassay of trypsin. A new aid in the assessment of pancreatic function.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Endobronchial balloon tamponade of hemoptysis in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Antimicrobial susceptibilities of rough, smooth, and mucoid colony types of Pseudomonas isolated from cystic fibrosis patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Results of 10 years of screening of newborn infants for inherited metabolic diseases in the province of Limburg (Belgium).</TITLE>
<TITLE>Comparative trial of manual and mechanical percussion technique with gravity-assisted bronchial drainage in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Paediatric Research Society. Plymouth, 15 and 16 September 1978: Abstracts.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn by meconium analysis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Pulmonary candidiasis in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Intestinal bile salts in cystic fibrosis: studies in the patient and experimental animal.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Possible hazard of timed-release aspirin in a patient with pancreatic insufficiency.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis with brain abscess.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis and hearing loss.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Vocational development and adjustment of adolescents with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Pharmacokinetics of azlocillin in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Dying children need help too.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: is it relevant to family practitioners?.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Inhibition of Tamm-Horsfall glycoprotein induction of alkaline phosphatase in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts by medium conditioned by normal cells.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Antibody responses to influenza virus vaccine in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Biological activities of cystic fibrosis serum. III. CF serum induced uptake of 45Ca++ by rabbit tracheal explants.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Differential concanavalin A binding of cystic fibrosis and normal liver alpha-L-fucosidase.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Enzyme immunoassay of albumin as an aid to the diagnosis of cystic fibrosis in the newborn human [proceedings].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Induction of alkaline phosphatase in cultured human fibroblasts. Comparison of normal cells and those from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Plasma membrane lipids of human diploid fibroblasts from normal individuals and patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>2. Theories of genetic causation in human disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bronchial artery embolization in the control of massive haemoptysis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in adults [editorial].</TITLE>
<TITLE>New mechanical aid to physiotherapy in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Evaluation of the forced expiration technique as an adjunct to postural drainage in treatment of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Dying children need help too.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Nocturnal elemental diet for retarded growth in a patient with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Lung function abnormalities in cystic fibrosis and changes during growth.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The role of nutritional status, airway obstruction, hypoxia and abnormalities in serum lipid composition in limiting exercise tolerance in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>One breath at a time: a family teaching program for children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Noninvasive radionuclide assessment of right ventricular performance in man.</TITLE>
<TITLE>In vitro susceptibility of pseudomonas to four beta-lactamantibiotics (ampicillin, cephalothin, carbenicillin, piperacillin), to four aminoglycosides (kanamycin, amikacin, gentamicin, tobramycin) and to colimycin.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Echocardiographic profiles of the long-term cardiac changes in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Lymphocytic acid-hydrolases and response to mitogens in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Measurement of regional lung function by tetrapolar electrical impedance plethysmography.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Evaluation of the single-breath diffusing capacity in asthma and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Echocardiographic abnormalities in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Response to bronchial provocation and exercise in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>IgE mediated hypersensitivity to pancreatic extract (PE) in parents of cystic fibrosis (CF) children.</TITLE>
<TITLE>A study of erythrocyte fatty acids, adenosinetriphosphatase and acetylcholinesterase in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Measurement of 4-hydroxyphenylacetic aciduria as a screening test for small-bowel disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Quality of sweat test performance in the diagnosis of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Secretion of beta-N-acetylglucosaminidase isoenzymes by cultured cystic fibrosis fibroblasts.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Glycosidases in serum of cystic fibrosis patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Carboxypeptidase B activity of cultured skin fibroblasts and relationship to cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Decreased sialic acid and altered binding to lectins of purified alpha 2-macroglobulin from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Abnormal distribution of alpha-L-fucosidase in cystic fibrosis: decreased activity in serum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Electrolytes and norepinephrine levels in blood of patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Primary amniotic fluid cell, skin fibroblast and liver alpha-L-fucosidase and its relation to cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Allergy in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Heterozygote advantage in cystic fibrosis: mosquito tests.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Deficiency of serum carboxypeptidase B-like (anaphylatoxin inactivator, carboxypeptidase N) activity in sera from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>False-positive 111In-labeled leukocyte scan in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Study of the oligosaccharide units from mucus glycoproteins of meconium from normal infants and from cases of cystic fibrosis with meconium ileus.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection: pathogenesis and therapy.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Lipids in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Obstruction of the respiratory pathways, its evaluation by methods of functional examination of the lungs and development in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Prenatal diagnosis of cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Clinical pharmacology in a paediatric hospital.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Protease deficiency in plasma of patients with cystic fibrosis. Reduced reaction of 4-methylumbelliferylguanidinobenzoate with plasma of patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Evaluation of long term tobramycin therapy in patients with cystic fibrosis and advanced pulmonary disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: decreased thermostability of alpha-mannosidase in crude extracellular fluids of patients and carriers.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Relationship between clinical conditions, radiographic findings and pulmonary functions in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Complement in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Substance P plasma levels in pregnancy and in various clinical disorders.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The effect of serum from patients with pancreatic disease on the short circuit current of rat jejunum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Defective cellular immunity to gram-negative bacteria in cystic fibrosis patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>High dosage tobramycin treatment of children with cystic fibrosis. Bacteriological effect and clinical ototoxicity.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The immotile-cilia syndrome and other ciliary diseases.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Tobramycin ototoxicity. Repeated courses of high dosage treatment in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Round table discussion--treatment of lower respiratory tract infections with co-trimoxazole.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Epidemiology of cystic fibrosis: a review.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The impact of grief: a retrospective study of family function following loss of a child with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Synthesis of hemoglobin Aic and related minor hemoglobin by erythrocytes. In vitro study of regulation.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serotypes and antibiotic susceptibilities of Pseudomonas aeruginosa isolates from single sputa of cystic fibrosis patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Dietary problems associated with the care of chronically sick children.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Inborn errors of metabolism: the need for sugar.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Therapeutic possibilities in Pseudomonas infections.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Multiple of isolates of Pseudomonas aeruginosa with differing antimicrobial susceptibility patterns from patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Summary of a workshop on infections in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Sulfhydryl-mediated depression of ciliary activity: an adverse effect of acetylcysteine.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Adult cystic fibrosis: a new therapeutic challenge for the primary care physician.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in Northern Ireland.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cutaneous necrotizing venulitis in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>HLA determinants in families with more than one member with cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Episodic arthritis in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Failure to thrive, anemia, and anasarca.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bronchial hyperreactivity in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>A peroral test of pancreatic insufficiency with 4-(N-acetyl-L-tyrosyl)aminobenzoic acid in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The effect of cimetidine on maldigestion in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Normal neutrophil and monocyte chemotaxis in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Hyperuricemia in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bronchial artery embolization in cystic fibrosis; technique and long-term results.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Reliability of sweat test in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>25-Hydroxycholecalciferol levels in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Reduced serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D concentration and disordered mineral metabolism in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum concentrations of 25-hydroxyvitamin D and 24,25-dihydroxyvitamin D in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Atypical cystic fibrosis of the pancreas with normal levels of sweat chloride and minimal pancreatic lesions.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Noninvasive evaluation of ventricular function in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Aminoglycoside clearance in patients with cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>A placebo-controlled trial of cephalexin therapy in the ambulatory management of patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>False positive sweat test, malnutrition, and the Mauriac syndrome.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in two black children with sickle cell anemia.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis and malnutrition.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Preatherosclerotic aortic lesions in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>PABA-test for diagnosis of exocrine pancreatic insufficiency [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Brain abscess and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Meconium ileus: laparotomy without resection, anastomosis, or enterostomy.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The effect of histamine, metiamide and cystic fibrosis factor on the electrophysiological properties of the frog's gastric mucosa [proceedings].</TITLE>
<TITLE>The chronically ligated submandibular salivary duct of the rabbit as a possible model for cystic fibrosis [proceedings].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Sweat tests [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>The sweat test for cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Immunoreactive serum trypsin in diseases of the pancreas.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Differential pathology of nasal polyps in cystic fibrosis and atopy.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Sensitive trypsin assay for dried-blood specimens as a screening procedure for early detection of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Detection of cystic fibrosis with plasma hydrolases [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Dried blood spot screening for cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Age dependence of serum angiotensin-converting enzyme activity [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Methylumbelliferyl-guanidinobenzoate reactive proteases and prenatal diagnosis of cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Screening for cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum-angiotensin-converting-enzyme in chronic granulomatous disease [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Dried-blood spot screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Allergy and bronchial hyperreactivity in cystic fibrosis [editorial].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum-immunoreactive-trypsin concentrations in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Methylumbelliferyl-guanidinobenzoate reactive proteases in amniotic fluid: possible marker for cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Plasma hydrolases in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Mechanical chest physiotherapy [editorial].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Detection of cystic fibrosis homozygotes and heterozygotes with plasma [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Arginine esterase in amniotic fluid: possible marker for cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Detection of cystic fibrosis homozygotes and heterozygotes with plasma.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Differential incorporation of 3H-thymidine into DNA in cultured skin fibroblasts derived from patients with cystic fibrosis and controls.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Animal model for cystic fibrosis: pulmonary clearance of Staphylococcus aureus in mice treated with reserpine.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Increased resistance to influenza as a possible source of heterozygote advantage in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Pathogenesis of cystic fibrosis: possible importance of alteration in epithelial surface topography.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Alkaline phosphatase induction in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Improved survival of patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Alkaline phosphatase induction in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>The short-term effects of chest physiotherapy on lung function tests in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Effect of four physiotherapy schedules on pulmonary function in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Relationship between clinical conditions, chest radiographic findings and respiratory function tests in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>A new percussion aid for cystic fibrosis patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The mechanism of autogenic drainage studied with flow volume curves.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Intestinal lactase deficiency in newborns with cystic fibrosis--dietary consequences.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Ultrastructure of the bronchial epithelium in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Recent research in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Relevance of second messengers in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Trace element malabsorption in exocrine pancreatic insufficiency.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Prostaglandins and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Operational definition of cystic fibrosis. I.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Alpha-glucosidase in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Postprandial total serum bile acid concentrations in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The cystic fibrosis gene, IgE and IgG4.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bronchial reactivity in children with cystic fibrosis and other recurrent or chronic bronchopulmonary diseases.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Increased serum TSH response to TRH in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Factors influencing the frequency of cystic fibrosis in South West Africa.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The effect of cystic fibrosis and non-cystic fibrosis plasma on electrophysiological responses in isolated frog gastric mucosa.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Fatty acid supplementation in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bronchial provocation tests in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The local immune status in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Complement activation and pulmonary inflammation in CF patients.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Protein, IgA, secretory IgA, IgG and electrolytes as parameters of parotid gland function in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Precipitating antibodies against E. coli, B. fragilis, and P. aeruginosa in CF patients and normal persons determined by means of crossed immunoelectrophoresis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Sulphated glycoproteins in the pancreas.</TITLE>
<TITLE>An evaluation of the meconium 'lactase test' for the detection of cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Two children with cystic fibrosis and myocardial fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Chemical comparison of normal and cystic fibrosis meconium: a quantitative and qualitative analysis of carbohydrate splitting enzymes.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The use and abuse of antibiotics, including in management of pulmonary manifestations in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Long-term tobramycin therapy in patients with cystic fibrosis and advanced pulmonary disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Bioavailability of oral antibiotics in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Progress in screening.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Diagnosing cystic fibrosis in adults [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Case records of the Massachusetts General Hospital. Weekly clinicopathological exercises. Case 8-1979.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Mitochondrial calcium uptake and oxygen consumption in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis and erroneous sweat tests.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: a disease of unknown causes.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Prone immersion physical exercise therapy in three children with cystic fibrosis: a pilot study.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Anemia, hypoproteinemia and edema in an infant with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum vitamin D and related mineral metabolism in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The pyridine scale for clinical measurement of olfactory threshold: a quantitative reevaluation.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in adults: an autopsy study.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Invited review. The technique and scope of electron-probe X-ray analysis in pathology.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Genetic aspects of pediatric lung disease.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Perspectives in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Increased heparin binding in cystic fibrosis: a reflection of altered glycoprotein biosynthesis?.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The chronically reserpinized rat as an animal model for cystic fibrosis: I. Acute effect of isoproterenol and pilocarpine upon pulmonary lavage fluid.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Altered polyamine metabolism in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Chronically reserpinized rat as a model for cystic fibrosis: Na+ transport inhibitory effect in submaxillary saliva.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Evidence against a specific effect of serum from patients with cystic fibrosis on sodium-dependent glucose transport in the rat jejunum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Altered intracellular calcium in fibroblasts from patients with cystic fibrosis and heterozygotes.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Anomalous alpha 2-macroglobulin-protease complexes in cystic fibrosis: decreased uptake of the complexes by fibroblasts in culture.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Inhibitory effect of cystic fibrosis serum on pseudomonas phagocytosis by rabbit and human alveolar macrophages.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum ciliotoxic activity in mutant mice with some hereditary alterations resembling cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Binding of 125I-labeled proteinases to plasma proteins in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum salivary amylase in cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Development of an improved tracheal explant bioassay for the detection of the ciliary dyskinesia factor in cystic fibrosis serum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Laser light-scattering spectroscopy: preliminary results on bioassay of cystic fibrosis factor(s).</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis serum effect on the short circuit current of rat jejunum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Detection of cystic fibrosis protein by isoelectric focusing of serum [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis protein, a confirmed diagnostic marker for detecting heterozygote carriers: significance in relation to future screening and to a proposed primary defect in alpha 2-macroglobulin.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Serum factor in cystic fibrosis: correlation with clinical parameters.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Intravenous linoleic acid supplementation in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>The chest roentgenogram in cystic fibrosis: a new scoring system.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Negative effects of oral fatty acid supplementation on sweat chloride in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Hypoelectrolytemia and metabolic alkalosis in infants with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Multifocal myocardial necrosis and fibrosis in pancreatic diseases of children.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Vitamin E: where do we stand?.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Metabolic alkalosis in infants with cystic fibrosis [letter].</TITLE>
<TITLE>An evaluation of the forced expiration technique as an adjunct to postural drainage.</TITLE>
<TITLE>A rapid procedure for the large scale purification of elastase and cathepsin G from human sputum.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Mitrochondrial NADH dehydrogenase in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: potential management through manipulation of the secretory process in affected exocrine glands.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Changing patterns of genetic counseling in a cystic fibrosis center.</TITLE>
<TITLE>New test to detect carriers of gene for cystic fibrosis [news].</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis--its surgical presentation.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Chemotherapy of chronic infections with mucoid Pseudomonas aeruginosa in lower airways of patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Proteins in bronchial secretion of children with chronic pulmonary diseases. I. Relation to clinical diagnosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Proteins in bronchial secretion of children with chronic pulmonary diseases. II. Relation to bronchoscopic and bronchographic examination.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Killing of fibroblasts by dexamethasone or dibutyryl adenosine 3',5'-monophosphate is not a valid test for cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Premature senescence in cultured skin fibroblasts from subjects with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in adolescents and young adults.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Implications of cystic fibrosis for health services and the afflicted.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: diagnosis, treatment, and prognosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Distal splenorenal shunt for decompression of portal hypertension in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: review of investigations of the mucociliary inhibitor.</TITLE>
<TITLE>"Small airways disease" in children: no test is best.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Detection of a lectin in the blood of cystic fibrosis homozygotes and heterozygotes.</TITLE>
<TITLE>Deficiencies of essential fatty acids and vitamin E in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE>
</RECORDS>